Guide to the Boone and Crockett Club Records circa 1885-2009
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Communications, 1904-2009; Series IV; 18.0 linear feet
  - Publications, 1910-2009; Subseries 1; 15.375 linear feet
    - Administration, 1910-2000; Sub-subseries 1; 3.75 linear feet
      - Records Book Dedications, undated (Box-folder 171/2)
      - Requested Returns Form Letters, undated (Box-folder 171/3)
      - Returned Publications, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 171/4)
      - Returns and Replacements, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 171/5)
      - Returns and Replacements, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 171/6)
      - Sales, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 171/7)
      - Sales and Distribution Reports, 2000 (Box-folder 171/8)
      - Sales and Order Ledger, 1981 (Box 222)
      - Samples, Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 171/9)
      - Special Inventory Reduction Sale for Members, undated (Box-folder 171/10)
      - Stackpole Books, Agreement and Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 171/11)
      - Talley Sheets for Books Sold, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 171/12)
      - Winchester Press, Contract, 1974 (Box-folder 171/13)
      - Wolfe Publishing Company, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 171/14 (1 of 2))
      - Wolfe Publishing Company, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 172/1 (2 of 2))
      - Wolfe Publishing Company, Jack Reneau, Correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 172/2)
    - Books, 1932-2001; Sub-subseries 2; 9.5 linear feet
      This sub-subseries is divided into two sub-sub-subseries and contains materials related to the books published by the Boone and Crockett Club.
      - Books - Records of North American Big Game, 1932-1994; Sub-sub-subseries 1; 6.75 linear feet
        The first edition of Records of North American Big Game was published by the Club in 1932 in conjunction with the National Collection of Heads and Horns. After 1952 Records books were published every six to seven years. In 1993 it was determined that Records books would be published every six years.
        This sub-sub-subseries contains materials from the first edition of Records of North American Big Game, published in 1932, through the tenth edition published in 1993. Materials include correspondence, drafts, signatures, proofs, and big game score charts.
        - Records of North American Big Game, 1st Edition, Brochures, 1932 (Box-folder 172/3)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 1st Edition, Correspondence and Clippings, 1932 (Box-folder 172/4)
        - North American Big Game, 2nd Edition, Correspondence, Invoices, and Receipts, 1936-1946 (Box-folder 172/5-7)
        - North American Big Game, 2nd Edition, Correspondence and Invoices, 1947-1951 (Box-folder 172/8)
        - North American Big Game, 2nd Edition, Illustrations, 1939 (Box-folder 172/9)
        - North American Big Game, 2nd Edition, Promotional Pamphlet, 1939 (Box-folder 172/10)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 3rd Edition, Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box-folder 241/3)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 3rd Edition, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Manuscript Drafts, 1951-1958 (Box-folder 172/11 (1 of 2))
        - Records of North American Big Game, 3rd Edition, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Manuscript Drafts, 1951-1958 (Box-folder 173/1 (2 of 2))
        - Records of North American Big Game, 3rd Edition, Royalty Statements, 1938-1952 (Box-folder 173/2)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 3rd Edition, Trophies Recorded in the Second Edition, 1947-1952 (Box-folder 173/3-4)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 4th Edition, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Manuscript Drafts, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 173/5-6)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Art, Photographs, and Plates, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 173/7)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Blacktail Deer Awards, Correspondence, 1964 (Box-folder 173/8)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Caribou Classification, 1964 (Box-folder 173/9)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Frank Close, Correspondence, 1964 (Box-folder 173/10)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Complimentary and Gift Copy Lists, 1964 (Box-folder 173/11)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Corrections for New Edition, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 173/12)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 174/1-6)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Cost, Sales, Profits, and Inventory, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 174/7)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Dedication, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 174/8)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Errors, 1948-1965 (Box-folder 174/9)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Fair Chase, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 174/10)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Foreword, Draft, 1964 (Box-folder 174/11)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Grizzly and Brown Bear Demarcation and Classification, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 175/1)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Grizzly and Brown Bear Revisions, 1964 (Box-folder 175/2)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Mailing Folder, Jacket Flaps, and Medallion Arts, 1964 (Box-folder 175/3)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Minimum Scores and Material, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 175/4)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Miscellaneous Material, 1964 (Box-folder 175/5)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Moose Ranges, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 175/6)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Mule and Blacktail Deer Range Changes, 1964 (Box-folder 175/7)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Orders and Invoices, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 175/8)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Outlines, Contents, and Assignments, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 175/9)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Promotional Correspondence, 1964 (Box-folder 175/10)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Publisher, Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 175/11)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Sagamore Hill Medal, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 175/12)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Sales Ledgers, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 175/13)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Stories Behind the Records, 1964 (Box-folder 175/14)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, The Books of the Boone and Crockett Club, Chapter by Milford Baker, 1964 (Box-folder 175/15)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 5th Edition, Dr. Phillip Wright, Classification, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 175/16)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Big Game Hunting and the Environmental Age, Chapter by the Honorable Russell E. Train, Drafts, Notes and Memoranda, 1970 (Box-folder 176/1)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Big Game of the Pleistocene, Chapter by John E. Guilday, Drafts, Notes and Memoranda, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 176/2)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Changing Hunting Practices, Chapter by John E. Rhea, Notes and Memoranda, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 176/3)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Chapters and Authors, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 176/4)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Chapter by Archibald Roosevelt, Correspondence, Drafts and Memoranda, 1971 (Box-folder 176/5)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Chapter by Lawrence C. Woods, Jr., Correspondence, Drafts and Notes, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 176/6)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Complimentary Copies, Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 176/7)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Consider the Meat Eaters, Chapter by Durwood L. Allen, Drafts, Notes and Memoranda, 1970 (Box-folder 176/8)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 176/9-11)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 241/4)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Cover, Dust Jacket, End Papers and Flyer, 1971 (Box-folder 176/12)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Dedication, 1971 (Box-folder 176/13)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Disbursements, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 176/14)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Disclaimer Clause, 1971 (Box-folder 176/15)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Distribution, 1958-1973 (Box-folder 177/1)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Field Notes on the Preservation of Big Game Trophies, Chapter by Robert H. Rockwell, Drafts, Notes, and Memoranda, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 177/2)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Form Letters Concerning Orders, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 177/3)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Information Requests, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 177/4)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Inquiry Reply Form Letters, 1971 (Box-folder 177/5)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Forward by Robert S. Waters, 1971 (Box-folder 177/6)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Frontispiece, 1971 (Box-folder 177/7)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Horns and Antlers, Chapter by Dr. Harold E. Anthony, Drafts, Notes and Memoranda, 1971 (Box-folder 177/8)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Illustrations, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 177/9)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Liability Clause, 1971 (Box-folder 177/10)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Miscellaneous Expenses, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 177/11)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Orders, 1975 (Box-folder 177/12)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Orders from American Rifleman, undated (Box-folder 177/13)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Photographs, 1971 (Box-folder 177/14)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Photograph, Correspondence, 1971 (Box-folder 177/15)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Printing Contract, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 177/16)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Publicity, 1972 (Box-folder 177/17)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Records Book Changes, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 177/18)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Relationships of Systematic Zoology to Big Game Records, Chapter by Dr. Charles F. Nadler, Notes and Memoranda, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 177/19)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Requests for Photographs, 1971 (Box-folder 177/20)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Score Charts, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 178/1)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Score Charts, Correspondence, and Memoranda, 1971 (Box-folder 178/2)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Score Tabulations, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 178/3)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Table of Contents, 1971 (Box-folder 178/4)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, The Books of the Boone and Crockett Club, Chapter by Milford J. Baker, Drafts, Notes and Memoranda, 1971 (Box-folder 178/5)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, The North American Wild Sheep, Chapter by Ian McTaggart Cowan and Valerius Geist, Drafts, Notes and Memoranda, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 178/6)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, The Official Scoring System of the North American Big Game Trophies, Chapter by Dr. Elmer M. Rusten, Drafts, Notes and Memoranda, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 178/7)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Title Page, 1971 (Box-folder 178/8)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Top Ranking Trophies by Species, 1971 (Box-folder 178/9)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Trophy Tabulations Transmittal, Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 178/10)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Ungava-Ugh! Or a Caribou Quest in Northern Kebec, Chapter by Duncan M. Hodgson, Drafts, Notes and Memoranda, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 178/11)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, What is a Trophy Head?, Chapter by Donald S. Hopkins, Drafts, Notes and Memoranda, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 178/12)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Wholesale Orders, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 178/13)
        - North American Big Game, 6th Edition, Philip L. Wright, Research on Trophy Listings, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 178/14)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Advertisement Distribution, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 178/15)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Big Game Rifles and Bullets, Chapter by William S. Brophy, Correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 178/16)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Book Promotion Summary, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 178/17)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Chapter Authors, Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 178/18)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Chapter Drafts, 1977 (Box-folder 178/19)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Clarification of Publication Duties, 1977 (Box-folder 178/20)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Complimentary Copy Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 178/21)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Copyright Certificate, 1977 (Box-folder 178/22)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Corrections, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 178/23)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 179/1-2)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Entry Into The Wilderness Society Conservation Award Program, 1978 (Box-folder 179/3)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Forward by Jack S. Parker, Correspondence and Drafts, 1977 (Box-folder 179/4)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Galley of Trophy Listings, 1976 (Box-folder 179/5-6)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Habitat-Essential Element in Big Game Management, Chapter by Daniel A. Poole and James B. Trefethen, Correspondence and Draft, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 179/7)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, History of Records Keeping for North American Big Game Trophies, Chapter by Samuel B. Webb, Correspondence and Draft, 1976 (Box-folder 179/8)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Hunter Education: The Great Challenge of the Third Century, Chapter by Ladd S. Gordon, Correspondence and Draft, 1976 (Box-folder 179/9)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Instructions for Printing Tabular Data, 1977 (Box-folder 179/10)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Mailing List, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 179/11-12)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Mechanicals and Photographs of Earlier Books, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 179/13)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Mountain Lions, Mule Deer, and Elk, Chapter by Maurice Hornocker, Correspondence and Drafts, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 179/14)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, National Rifle Association, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1964-1977 (Box-folder 179/15)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Prints for Record Book, Correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 179/16)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Recipient Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 241/5)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Reviews and Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 179/17 (1 of 8))
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Reviews and Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 180/1-7 (7-8 of 8))
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Review of the Wild Sheep in North America, Chapter by Philip L. Wright, Draft, undated (Box-folder 180/8)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Score Charts, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 180/9)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Score Chart Changes Needed, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 180/10)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Signatures, 1977 (Box-folder 181/1)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Signatures, Second Printing, 1978 (Box-folder 181/2-3)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Suggestions for Promotion and Merchandising, 1977 (Box-folder 181/4)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, The American Black Bear, Chapter by Lynn Rogers, Correspondence and Drafts, 1976 (Box-folder 181/5)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, The Management of Mountain Sheep, Chapter by Valerius Geist, Draft, 1976 (Box-folder 181/6)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, The North American Big Game Awards Program, Chapter by William H. Nesbitt, Correspondence and Drafts, 1976 (Box-folder 181/7)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Wilderness World Limited, Prints, Correspondence, 1977 (Box-folder 181/8)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Wildlife Photography, Chapter by Richard Borden, Correspondence and Drafts, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 181/9)
        - North American Big Game, 7th Edition, Wolf Research on Isle Royale, by Durward L. Allen, Drafts, 1976 (Box-folder 181/10)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Annotated First Pass, 1981 (Box-folder 181/11)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Authors, Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 182/1)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Chapters, Correspondence and Drafts, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 182/2-4)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Chapters, Type-Spaced with Edits, 1981 (Box-folder 182/5-6)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Color Plate Sections, Correspondence, 1981 (Box-folder 182/7)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Corrected First Pass, 1981 (Box-folder 182/8)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Corrected First Pass of Trophy Data Series, 1981 (Box-folder 183/1-3)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Cover and Dust Jacket, 1981 (Box-folder 183/4)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Cover Stamping and Dust Jacket, 1981 (Box-folder 183/5)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Cut Lines for Photographs, 1981 (Box-folder 183/6)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Drafts and Corrections, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 183/7-8)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Flyer, Galley Proofs, 1981 (Box-folder OS 219/x)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Form Letters, 1981 (Box-folder 183/9)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Front Matter Drafts and Corrections, 1981 (Box-folder 183/10)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Galley Proofs, 1981 (Box-folder OS 223/x)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Haddon Contract Invoices, 1981 (Box-folder 183/11)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Jacket Art, Galley Proofs, 1981 (Box-folder 183/12)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Limited Edition Version, 1981 (Box-folder 183/13)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Orders, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 184/1-2)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Page Proof Master Set, 1981 (Box-folder 184/3)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Promotional Correspondence, 1981 (Box-folder 184/4)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Replacement Books, Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 184/5)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Score Charts, 1981 (Box-folder 184/6)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Trophy Acceptance Forms, 1980 (Box-folder 184/7)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Typesetting, 1981 (Box-folder 184/8)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 8th Edition, Uncorrected Draft of Trophy Data Series, 1981 (Box-folder 184/9-10)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 9th Edition, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1988 (Box-folder 185/1)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 9th Edition, Courtesy Responses, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 185/2)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 9th Edition, Flyer, Color Separations and Galley Proofs, 1988 (Box-folder OS 219/x)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 9th Edition, Line Art, 1986 (Box-folder 185/3)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 9th Edition, Member Mailer, Galley Proofs, 1988 (Box-folder OS 219/x)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 9th Edition, Score Charts, 1981 (Box-folder 185/4)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 10th Edition, Complimentary Copy Recipient Ledger, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 185/5)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 10th Edition, Correspondence, 1993 (Box-folder 185/6)
        - Records of North American Big Game, 10th Edition, Orders, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 185/7)
        - Records of North American Big Game, Limited Edition, Member Mailer, 1981 (Box-folder 185/8)
      - Books - Other, 1954-2001; Sub-sub-subseries 2; 2.75 linear feet
        In addition to the Records of North American Big Game books, the Boone and Crockett has published editions on wild sheep, record whitetail and mule deer as well as record elk. The club has also published books on hunting and conservation. This sub-sub-subseries contains correspondence, drafts, proofs, mailers and reviews related to these publications.
        - A Century of Conservation: The Boone and Crockett Club, 1897-1987, by George B. Ward, Draft, 1986 (Box-folder 185/9-10)
        - A History of the Boone and Crockett Club, by William Sheldon, Draft, undated; This folder contains only the table of contents and four pages of Sheldon's mansucript. A digitized copy of the complete manuscript is online: https://scholarworks.umt.edu/sheldon/ (Box-folder 185/11)
        - An American Crusade for Wildlife, Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 185/12)
        - An American Crusade for Wildlife, Typesetting and Board for Insert, 1985 (Box-folder 185/13)
        - An American Crusade for Wildlife, 2nd Edition, Galley Proof, 1985 (Box-folder OS 219/x)
        - An American Crusade for Wildlife, Unfilled Orders, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 241/6)
        - Centennial History of the Boone and Crockett Club, by George B. Ward, Correspondence, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 185/14)
        - Crusade for Wildlife, Art Work, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 185/15)
        - Crusade for Wildlife, Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 185/16)
        - Crusade for Wildlife, Dust Jacket, 1961 (Box-folder 185/17)
        - Crusade for Wildlife, James B. Trefethen, Progress Reports, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 185/18)
        - From the Peace to the Fraser, Publishing Proposals and Invoices, 1994 (Box-folder 185/19)
        - Game in the Desert, Copyright Issues, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 185/20)
        - How to Measure and Score Big Game Trophies, Correspondence, 1963-1974 (Box-folder 185/21)
        - How to Measure and Score Big Game Trophies, Correspondence and Schedule, 1982 (Box-folder 185/22)
        - Measuring and Scoring North American Big Game Trophies, 1st Edition, Color Separations and Drafts, undated (Box-folder 186/1)
        - Measuring and Scoring North American Big Game Trophies, Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 186/2)
        - Measuring and Scoring North American Big Game Trophies, Flyer, Galley Profs, 1985 (Box-folder OS 219/x)
        - Member Hunt Story Book, Articles, Correspondence, and Drafts, 1974-1986 (Box-folder 186/3-4)
        - Modern North American Big Game Hunting, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 186/5)
        - Modern North American Big Game Hunting, Winchester Press Agreement, 1974 (Box-folder 186/6)